Guide to the Verse Records 1984-2008
University of Chicago Library
- Series I: Correspondence
  - Subseries 1: Alphabetical
    - Ll-Ly, 1992-2008, Lloyd, Emily Loberer, Eric Lobko, William Lock, Charles Lock, Norman Locke, Christopher Loden, Rachel Logan, William Lombardo, Gina Long, Judy Longenbach, James Longfellow, Stephen Longley, Michael Lonoconus, Michele Lopez, Maggie López-Colomé, Pura Lorberer, Eric Lorenz, Scott Lori, Erudite Loudermelt, C.L. Loughran, Michael Lourie, Dick Love, B.J. Lovejoy, Sue Lowery, Joanne Loydell, Rupert Lozar, Tom Lubasch, Lisa Luck, Richard Ludvigson, Susan Luftig, Richard Lumsden, Alison Lumsden, Roddy Lundbom, Erika Lutz, Gary Lyalin, Natalie Lynch, Alessandra Lynch, Anthony Lynn, Heidi Lynn, Richard (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - M-Marks, 1992-2008, MacCarter, Kent MacGregor, Elizabeth MacGowan, Christopher MacKenzie, Jennifer Mackenzie, Sinead Madrid, Anthony Magazzi, Josef Maginnes, Al Mailer, N. Malech, Dora Maliszewski, Paul Mandel, Charlotte Mandle, Dara Manesiotis, Joy Mangeot, Andre Mangold, Sarah Manguso, Sarah Manirao, Mani Manning, Nicholas March, Thomas Marcinkowski, Michael Marcus, Ben Mariani, Paul Mark, P.J. Mark, Sabrina Markham, Malinda Marklevits, Farah Marks, Justin (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Marku-Max, 1997-2008, Markus, David Markus, Peter Marshall, Tod Martin, Christine Martin, Christopher Martin, Ross Martin, Jynne Martinez, Dionisio Marvin, Cate Marx, Beth Anderson Marx, John Mason, David Mateer, John Mathias, Louise Mathys, Ted Matthews, Clay Matthias, John Mattox, Gretchen Matze, Mary Maugeri, Carolina Maxwell, Glyn Maxwell, Kristi Maxwell, Susan (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - May-McC, 1986-2007, May, Alan Mazer, Ben Mazis, Glen McCallum, Shara McCarthy, Brian McClatchy, J.D. McCollough, Aaron McCooey, David McCord, Kyle McCorkle, James McCormick, Paul McCrae, Shane McCrorie, Edward (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - McDermott, Chris, 2000-2006 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - McD-McGuin, 1987-2007, McDonald, Stanley McDonnell, Sean McFadden, Kevin McFarland, Erin McGann, Jerome McGlynn, Karyna McGuinness, Kelly (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - McGuir-McPhe, 1987-2005, McGuire, Jerry McHugh, Heather McKee, Marc McKendrick, Jamie McKernan, John McKinsey, Martin McManus, Kevin McMichael, James McMullen, Joanne McPherson, Sandra (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - McPhi-Mela, 1989-2008, McPhillips, Robert McSweeney, Joyelle Mead, Jane Meier, Richard Melamed, Lori (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Meli-Mill, 1992-2007, Melicker, Todd Melvin, Lydia Mendoza, Mark Mengert, Christina Mengham, Rod Merchant, Preston Merrill, James Merriman, Emily Meserve, Susie Messerli, Douglas Metzger, Teresa Meyer, Daniel Meyer, Nadine Middleton, David Militello, Jennifer Millager, Abby Miller, Errol Miller, Greg Miller, Michael Miller, Sandra Miller, Sid Miller, Wayne (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Miln-Mora, 1985-2007, Milne, Drew Minter, Peter Mir, Stan Mirskin, Jerry Mister, Andrew Moeckel, W. Thorpe Moffitt, John Mohammed, K. Silem Mohring, Ron Molini, Sally Monacell, Pete Moni, Natasha Monk, Ian Monroe, Jonathan Monson, Ander Montney, Marvin Moore, Catherine Moore, George Moran, Mike (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Morg-My, 1985-2007, Morgan, Andrew Morgan, Robert Mori, Bruna Moriarty, Laura Moritz, Rachel Mormoris, Stephen Morris, Darren Morris, Katie Morris, Ronn Morrison, Rusty Morrissette, Micaela Mörsel Nathan, Miriam Mosca, Mark Moschovakis, Anna Moss, Jennifer Mosson, Gregg Motion, Andrew Mott, Michael Moxley, Jennifer Mueller, Jenny Muldoon, Paul Murabito, Stephen Muratori, Fred Murnane, Catherine Murphy, Jim Murphy, Kay Murphy, Ryan Murray, Christopher Murray, Les Muske, Carol Myers, Gina (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - N-Nic, 1996-2007, Nacca, Judy Naci, Lorin Nagler, David Nandakumar, Prema Neimeyer, Robert Nelligan, Marci Nelson, Jason Nelson, Maggie Nelson, Timothy Nesset, Kirk Nester, Daniel Newkirk, Kent Newman, Lance Newton, Keith Nezhukumatahil, Aimee Nichols, Travis (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Nie-Nu, 1995-2007, Nied, Susanna Niewoehner, Virginia Nightingale, Andrew Nikolayev, Philip Njatin, Lela Norcliffe, James Norris, Gary Norton, Romana Noteboom, Michelle Nowrousian, Schirin Novak, Boris Nudelman, Edward Nurhussein, Nadia Nussbaum, Martha Nutter, Geoffrey (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - O, 1986-2007, O’Brien, George O’Connor, Brendan Odell, Jere O’Donoghue, Bernard O’Driscoll, Dennis Offen, Ron O’Hara, Sean Olin, Jessica Olney, James Olstein, Lisa Omanson, Bradley O’Reilly, Caitriona Orff, Valerie Orlemanski, Julie Ormond, Timothy Orr, Gregory Osborn, Andrew Osman, Jena Ossip, Kathleen O’Toole, Peter (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - P-Pap, 1987-2007, Padel, Ruth Padgett, Ron Paegle, Julia Pafunda, Danielle Paisky, Robert Palm, Lars Palmer, Michael Pandiri, Thalia Pankey, Eric Papa, Joseph Papadopoulos, Stephanos (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Paquin, Ethan, 1996-2005 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Par-Pep, 1992-2007, Parini, Jay Parker, Seth Parko, Kim Paterson, Don Paterson, James Cameron Patterson, Juliet Pau-Llosa, Ricardo Pavelich, David Pavlic, Ed Peacock, Molly Pearson, Ted Peary, Alexandria Pecqueur, Jean-Paul Pendergast, Dawn Penna, J.J. Peoples, Peg Peppermint, Heidi (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Per-Pin, 1985-2007, Perchik, Simon Perelman, Bob Perloff, Marjorie Perriere, Donna Pesch, Josef Peters, Cheri Peterson, Kathleen Pethybridge, Jeffrey Petlevski, Sibila Petrescu, Ioanna Petrosino, Kiki Pfeifer, Teresa Phillips, Carl Phillips, Lance Pierce, Scott Pilch, Jennifer Pinkerton, Daniel Pinsky, Robert (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Pio-Pu, 1985-2008, Piombino, Nick Pitts, Kathy Plasek, Aaron Plumly, Stanley Polikoff, Daniel Polito, Robert Pollack, Frederick Pollard, Derek Pollock, James Ponce de Leon, Maria Ponka, Vince Pople, Ian Porter, Dorothy Porter, Esther Post, Chad Potokar, Jure Potter, Jane Potter, Steve Poucel, Jean-Jacques Powell, Elizabeth Powell, Jim Powell, John Preston, Dorine Prevallet, Kristin Prevost, Chad Price, Michael Pringle, Kathryn Pritts, Nathan Prufer, Kevin Prunty, Wyatt Pugh, Christina Pulkkinen, Kristin Pultz, Constance Purdy, Gilbert Pursley, John Pustateri, Chris (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Q, 1987-2006, Qualls, Suzanne Queeney, Courtney Quinn, Alice Quinn, Carol Quinn, Justin (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Ra, 1985-2007, Rabinowitz, Anna Radcliff, Lisa Rafdal, Kristin Rahmark, Sabrina Rail, Evan Raine, Craig Ramazani, Fabian Ramke, Bin Ramos, Peter Rampp, Charles Ramsay, Steve Ramsdell, Heather Ramspeck, Doug Rand, Jordan Rankine, Claudia Raos, Andrea Rasmovicz, Bill Rasula, Jed Rathkamp, Josh Raven, Francis (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Re-Ri, 1989-2007, Rebele, Tara Reddy, Srikanth (Chicu) Redgrove, Peter Reeves, Sonya Reid, Alastair Reid, Christopher Reidel, James Reilly, Evelyn Reimer, Karen Reis, Donna Remein, Daniel Revell, Donald Reyes, Barbara Jane Reynolds, Charles Reynolds, Rebecca Rhee, Michelle Young-Mee Rich, Jordana Rich, Peter Rich, Rita Richards, Barbara Richardson, Rachel Richman, Robert Richmond, Andrew Ricks, Christopher Riesterer, Kory Rigby, Karen Riggs, Sarah Rivard, David (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Rob-Roh, 1998-2005, Robbins, Michael Roberson, Ed Roberts, Andrew Michael Roberts, Garrett Roberts, M. Edwin Roberts, Michael Roberts, Tim Robertson, Lisa Robinette, Robert Robins, Michael Robinson, Anthony Robinson, Elizabeth Robinson, Monica McFawn Rodefer, Stephen Roderick, Brian Rodger, William Rodriguez, David Jr. Rogers, Michelle Rohrer, Matthew (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Roo-Ry, 1985-2006, Root, William Rose, Peter Rose, Rachel Rosemurgy, Catie Rosenb(?), Susan Rosenberg, Dan Rosenthal, Mira Rosser, J. Allyn Roth, Matthew Rotstein, Jason Roundy, Richard Rowe, Ronald Rudman, Mark Rumsey, Tessa Ruppersburg, Hugh Ryan, Gig Ryan, Tracy (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Sa, 1997-2005, Saalfeld, Daniel Sadre-Orafal, Jenny Sage, Andrew Saint, Harry Saje, Natasha Salamun, Tomaz Salane, Jeffrey Salerno, Christopher Salter, Mary Jo Samyn, Mary Ann Sanchez, Jorge Sandage, Chivas Sanders, Tony Sansom, Ian Sant, Andrew Santos, Ron Sapinkopf, Lisa Satterfield, Jane Savich, Zach Savitz, Michael Sawyer, Ryan (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Sca-Schoenb, 1977-2006, Scanlon, Christine Schaefer, Standard Schapira, Kate Schauffler, Zanni Scheele, Christof Scheele, Roy Scheiwe, Richard Schiavo, Michael Schickling, Jared Schiff, Robyn Schilpp, Margot Schlegel, Rob Schmeer, Matthew Schmidt, Michael Schneider, Ronald Schoenberger, Nancy (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Schoenf-Sco, 1993-2006, Schoenfeld, Becky Schofield, Don Schreyer, Alice Schroeder, Amy Schroeder, Steven Schuchard, Ronald Schuldt, Morgan Schultz, Susan Schuman, Dave Schutz, Lacy Schwartz, Leonard Schwartz, Louis Schwartz, Naomi Schwartzman, Adam Scott, Herbert Scott, Jeanie (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Se-Shind, 1997-2008, Seay, Allison Sebald, W.G. Seeger, Roy Selby, Don Selby, Spencer Seligman, Howie Sellers, Danielle Senfert, Christopher Sewell, David Shah, Pankaj Shapcott. Jo Sharma, Prageeta Shaw, Kent Shea, Daniel Shea, James Shearn, Amy Sheck, Laurie Shepherd, Reginald Sherborne, Craig Sherman, Ann Shimoda, Brandon Shindell, Matthew (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Shine, Lori, 2002-2007 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Ship-Shu, 1985-2006, Shipley, Vivian Shippy, Peter Shivani, Anis Shoaf, Diann Shobert, Adam Shoptaw, John Short, Spencer Shuttle, Penelope (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Si-Sik, 1985-2005, Siegel, Robert Sigalas, Mary Signorelli-Pappas, Rita Sikelianos, Eleni (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Sil-Sl, 1986-2006, Silano, Martha Silem Mohammad, Kasey Silliman, Ron Silver, Kristen Simeon, Berry Simic, Charles Simon, Aaron Simon, Maurya Simonds, Sandra Simons, Lacy Simonson, J’Lyn Simpson, Louis Sims, Laura Sirhal, Dan Sittler, Lee Skinner, C.J. Skloot, Floyd Slaymaker, Bob Slease, Marcus (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Smith, B-D, 1988-2004, Smith, Bruce Smith, Carmen Smith, Dale Smith, Dave (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Smith, E-T, 1985-2006, Smith, Ernest Smith, Joshua Smith, Justin Smith, Lytton Smith, Marcus Smith, Matthew Smith, Matthew Alan Smith, Michael Smith, Rebecca Smith, Rod Smith, Ron Smith, S. Smith, Todd (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Sn-So, 1997-2005, Snediker, Michael Snodgrass, Ann Snodgrass, Kathleen Snodgrass, W.D. Snow, Carol Snyder, Gary Snyder, Laurel Snyder, Lauren Sobin, Gustaf Sofaer, Daniel Sol, Adam Solfrian, Joanna Solomon, Laura Solomon, Onna Sommer, Piotr Sommerville, Jane Sorkin, Adam (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Sp-Ste, 1986-2007, Spahr, Juliana Speaker, Mary Spires, Elizabeth Sprague, Jane Spring, Declan Srivastava, Satyendra Stallworthy, Jon Stambler, Douglas Stamey, Vince Stanford, Donald Stanic, Barbara Stanley, Rose Ann Stanton, Maura Staples (Peppermint), Heidi Staples, John Starr, Leslie Starzinger, Page Hill Stebelton, Chuck Steele, Peter Steensen, Sasha Stefans, Brian Steger, Ales Steinberg, Hugh Steinhoff, Eirik Stelzer, Skaidrite Stephens, Nathalie Sterud, Sommer Stevick, Mark Stewart, Lane Stewart, Susan (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Sti-Sw, 1995-2006, Stiles, John Stock, Norman Stoloff, Carolyn Stomel, Robert Stone, Alison Stonecipher, Donna Story, Julia Stowell-Travis, Phyllis Straka, Vanda Strang, Brian Strauss, Adam Strong, Christina Struloeff, John Stuart-Smith, Stephen Stucky, Janaka Stumpf, Jason Sturgeon, Shawn Suermondt, Tim Sulej, Peter Sumegi, Veronica Sumrall, Daniel Summer, Laurie Sundahl, Daniel Sutherland, Keston Sutter, Paul Sutton-Ramspeck, Doug Svaliana, Mathias Swann, Brian Sweeney, Chad Sweeney, Matthew Swensen, Cole Swierenga, Marianne Swift, Todd (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - T-Tom, 1987-2007, Tabios, Eileen Tall, Deborah Tanerai, Javant Taransky, Michelle Taufer, Veno Taylor, Catherine Taylor, Emily Taylor, Sam Teare, Brian Tedesco, Cynthia Teicher, Craig Thackrey, Susan Theune, Michael James Thirkfield, Jonathan Thomas, Heather Thomas, Jamie Thomas, Susan Thomas, Tracy Thompson, Christina Thompson, Jon Thompson, Kyle Thompson, Phillip Thompson, Tom Thomson, Henry Thorburn, Matthew Tibbetts, Frederick Tiger, Madeline Tillona, Carl Todd, Cody Todd, John Tolf, Gale Tolhurst, Hugh Tomash, Barbara (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Ton-Ty, 1997-2007, Tonelli, Chris Toohill, Heather Topalian, Suzanne Tost, Tony Tranter, John Tremaine, Louis Trivedi, Amish Tromp, Ian Tuck, Zack Tucker, Seth Tuffield, Aviva Turnmire, Margie Tweedy, Colin Twemlow, Nicholas Tynes, Jennifer (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - U, 1996-2005, Umans, Kate Unwin, Vanessa Upton, Lee Urbanski, Debbie (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - V, 1987-2007, Valles, Alissa VanDoorn, Ashley Van Ness, Gordon Vap, Sarah Varrone, Kevin Vazlrani, Reetika Veith, Danielle Vendler, Helen Vennedy, Said Villaneuva, Tino Vincz, Jason Vines, Adam Viridian, Paul Vitiello, Christopher Vogelsang, Arthur Volkman, Karen Volkmeier, Rick (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - W-Walla, 1996-2007, Wade, Sidney Wagner, Cathy Wagner, James Wagner, Jasmine Dreame Wahl, Dan Wakamatsu, Kayoko Wald, Diane Waldner, Liz Waldnor, Peter Waldrep, G.C. Waldrop, Keith Waldrop, Rosmarie Walker, Jane Walker, Nicole Wallace, Gavin Wallace, Mark Wallace, Toby Wallace-Crabbe, Christopher (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Walle-We, 1993-2007, Wallenstein, Barry Walsh, William Waltz, William Wanen, Rosanna Ward, Fritz Ward, Tony Ward, William Wardrop, Daneen Warren, Robert Penn Wasley, Aidan Watson, Emily Watson, Maurice Watson, Stephen Webb, Charles Webster, Derek Webster, Kerri Weddle, Jeff Wehle, Ellen Weiner, Joshua Weinstein, Carole Weisburd, Stefi Wellnitz, Clare Wenderoth, Joe West, Simon Weston, Lorraine (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Wh, 1997-2007, Whalen, John Wheatley, David Whedon, Tony White, Derek White, Jared White, Mark White, Mike White, Naomi White, Philip Whitehead, Gary Whitmarsh, Jason (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Wic-Will, 1989-2004, Wicks, Les Widner, Nikki Wiegers, Michael Wiener, Chet Wier, Dara Wilbur, Richard Wilde-Menozzi, Willis Wilkinson, John Wilkinson, Josuha Wilks, Lucy Willeford, Ann Williams, Diane Williams, Ian Williams, Kenneth Williams, Phil Willis, Christina Willis, Elizabeth Willkinson, Poppy (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Wils-Wo, 1991-2005, Wilson, Emily Wilson, Fiona Wilson, James Wilson, Rob Wilson, Ryan Winch, Terence Winter, Jonah Winter, Kathleen Winter, Max Wisniewski, Mark Wojahn, David Wolff, Rebecca Wong, Suzi Wood, Joseph Wootten, Devon (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Wr-Wy, Wright, Anne Wright, Carolyne Wright, Charles Wright, Harriet Wright, Katherine Wright, Paul Wuest, Charles Wysong, Brennen (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Y-Z, 1996-2006, Yakich, Mark Yarbrough, John Yarbrough, Wynn Yau, John Yezzi, David Yorty, Thomas Young, Andy Young, David Young, Dean Young, Elizabeth Young, Gary Young, Kevin Yurkovsky, Alexandra Zaiss, David Zanelli, Alessio (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Zapruder, Matthew, 1998-2005 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Zapruder, Matthew, 1998-2005 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Zapruder, Matthew, 1998-2005 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Zapruder, Matthew, 1998-2005 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Zar-Zy, 1996-2006, Zaretsky, Natalia Zawacki, Benjamin Zhang, Jenny Zherlsch, Leonard Zhicheng-Mingde, Desmond Ziegler, Anna Ziman, Larry Zucker, Rachel Zultanski, Steven Zupan, Uros Zura, Gregory Zuzga, Jason Zwart, Jane Zwartjes, Arianne Zweizig Suzanne Zydek, Frederick (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Unidentified, 1995-2006 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 2: Editorial
    - Editorial, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Editorial, 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Editorial, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Editorial, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Editorial, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Editorial, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Editorial, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Editorial, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Editorial, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Editorial, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Editorial, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Editorial, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Editorial, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Editorial, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Editorial, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Editorial, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Editorial, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Editorial, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Editorial, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Editorial, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Editorial, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Editorial, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Editorial, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Editorial, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Editorial, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Editorial, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Editorial, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Editorial, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Editorial, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Editorial, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Editorial, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Editorial, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Editorial, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Editorial, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Editorial, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Series II: Administrative and Events
  - Author Biographies, undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - The Best Australian Poems 2004, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - The Best Australian Poems 2004, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Compact Discs, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Festival, Edinburgh International Festival, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Festival, First Festival of Literary Magazines, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Festival, PEN World Voices Festival, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Festival, Verse Festival, Photos, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Grant Applications, The Australian Arts Council, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Grant Applications, The Scottish Arts Council, 1995-2000 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Grant Applications, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Handbills, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Harper's Magazine, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - International Verse Prize, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Invoices, 1989-1992 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Invoices, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Invoices, 2001-2003 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Invoices, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Mailing List, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Memorandum of Agreement, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Memorandum of Agreement, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1985-1996 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Notes, undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Permission to Publish, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Permission to Publish, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Permission to Publish, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Photocopies of Poems, undated (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Poetry Readings, Andrew Zawacki, 2003-2004 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Poetry Readings, Phillis Levin, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Press Releases, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Press Releases, 2001-2002 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Press Releases, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Printing, 1996-2001 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Printing, 2006-2007 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Promotional Material, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Publicity, 1992-2003 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Pushcart Prize Nominee, 1999-2001 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Russia Trip, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - “A Short Version of Verse,” 2005 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Skein Issue 2, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Submissions, 1987-1993 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Submissions, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Submissions, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Submissions, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Submissions, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Submissions, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Submissions, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Submissions, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Submissions, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Submissions, 1997-2001 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Submissions, 1998-1999 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Submissions, 1998-2001 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Submissions, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Submissions, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Submissions, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Submissions, 2001-2002 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Submissions, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Submissions, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Submissions, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Submissions, 2004-2005 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Submissions, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Submissions, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Submissions, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Submissions, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Submissions, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Submissions, undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Submissions, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Submissions, undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Submissions, Accepted Material, 1998-2001 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Submissions, Accepted Material, 1998-2001 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Submissions, Accepted Material, 1998-2001 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Submissions, Adams, Carrie Olivia, 2006 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Submissions, Book Reviews, 1995-1999 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Submissions, Book Reviews, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Submissions, Book Reviews, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Submissions, Browne, Sir Thomas, undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Submissions, Celona, Tina, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Submissions, Cohen, Lyndsey, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Submissions, Ficarra, Elise, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Submissions, Interviews, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Submissions, Interviews, 1997-2003 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Submissions, Interviews, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Submissions, McDermott, Chris, undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Submissions, McDermott, Chris, undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Submissions, Morgan, Andrew, undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Submissions, Morgan, Elizabeth, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Submissions, Rejected Material, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Submissions, Rejected Material, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Submissions, Rejected Material, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Submissions, Rejected Material, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Submissions, Rejected Material, 1998-2002 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Submissions, Rejected Material, 2001-2002 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Submissions, Rejected Material, 2001-2002 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Submissions, Rejected Material, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Submissions, Schavel, Steve, undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Submissions, Sweeney, Chad, 2006 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Submissions, Watson, Maurice T., 2000 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Submissions, Whitmarsh, Jason, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Submissions, Williams, Diane, undated (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Subscriptions, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Subscriptions, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Wave Books, Royalties, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Verse Press, Letters to Wendy’s, 1996-2001 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Series III: Journal Issues
  - Issue 4, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Volume 4:1, Canadian Poetry Feature, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Volume 4:3, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Volume 5:2, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Volume 7:1, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Volume 7:3, The New Formalism In American Poetry, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Volume 7:3, The New Formalism In American Poetry, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Volume 8:1, John Ashbery's Influence on Contemporary Poetry, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Volume 8:1, John Ashbery's Influence on Contemporary Poetry, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Volume 8:3/9:1, Donald Justice Special Feature, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Volume 10:3, Amy Clampitt, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Volume 10:3, Amy Clampitt, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Volume 11:2, Derek Wolcott: Poems and Essays on His Work, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Volume 12:3, Richard Hugo Feature, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Volume 13:1, Prose Poem Feature, 1995-1996 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Volume 13:2-3, Prose Poem Feature, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Volume 14:2, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Volume 15:1-2, Scottish Poets, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Volume 15:1-2, Scottish Poets, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Volume 15:3/16:1, Australian Poetry Feature, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Volume 15:3/16:1, Australian Poetry Feature, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Volume 15:3/16:1, Australian Poetry Feature, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Volume 16:2, Women Irish Poets, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Volume 16:2, Women Irish Poets, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Volume 16:2, Women Irish Poets, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Volume 16:3/17:1, 1999-2000 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Volume 17:2-3/18:1, Mexican Poetry Feature, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Volume 19:1-2, The Prose Issue, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Volume 19:3/20:1, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Volume 19:3/20:1, 2003 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Volume 19:3/20:1, 2003 (Box 31, Folder 2)